tcixps.com 2017-11-20

# Leading Courier and Logistics Companies, Air Express Cargo - TCIEXPRESS

OVERVIEW

We understand and respect your concerns about privacy. Please read our privacy policy before using the Website. It indicates the information we collect and actions we take to secure any personal information you may choose to provide while using the site, as well as how we collect it and use it.  www.tciexpress.in does not share any of this information with other parties.

DATA SECURITY

www.tciexpress.in uses standard measures to ensure the security of any personal information you provide. Unfortunately, there is no guarantee that information transmitted over the Internet is absolutely secure. Therefore, although www.tciexpress.in takes reasonable measures to ensure your data, we cannot guarantee the security of your transmissions and you do so at your own risk. After transmission, we will use industry standard measures to secure your information.

COOKIES

A "cookie" is a small piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Currently, we do not use cookies in any of the pages. We sometimes collect anonymous information from visits to our website to help us provide better customer service. This anonymous information is sometimes known as "click stream data". We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide you with a better customer service. Cookies can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website.

LINKS

This website contains links to other websites. TCI Express Limited is not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of such websites, nor do we take any responsibility for the opinions of third parties expressed on or through our website.

CONTACTING THE WEBSITE

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact: [ info@tciexpress.in](mailto:info@tciexpress.in)

DISCLAIMER

TCI Express Limited reserves the right to modify or update its Privacy Policy at any time without notice, so we encourage you to review this policy from time to time.
